{
    "id": "20aa4dc5e2164811981c70843ccf8b61",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ………………… .. the charge of trespassing into the compound.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "denied",
                "refused",
                "declined"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The scheme ………………… .. for want of sufficient support from the members.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fell off",
                "fell out",
                "fell through"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We feared that it would rain any time since the sky was …………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "overclouded",
                "overcast",
                "overlaid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His speech was so interesting that I was all …………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eyes",
                "ears",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are forty teachers …………………… .. the staff roll.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was glad to hear of his recovery …………………… . a critical illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "after",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Modern science grew …………………… . the influence of scientists such as Copernicus, Kepler, Galileo and Newton.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "under",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………… the influence of alcohol.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A servant is expected to ………………… . the orders of his master.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carry on",
                "carry over",
                "carry out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There …………………… .. a war over it, but in the end reason prevailed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can be",
                "could be",
                "could have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}